UNITED UNIVERSITY PROFESSIONS (UUP) RECORDS (APAP039) 1964-2000
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subgroup VI: Labor Relations-Negotiations, 1968-1999; 9; 25.73
  - Series 1: Negotiations by Contract Year, 1971-1974 Contract to 1999-2003 Contract; 9.1; 9.53
    - Subseries 1.9 - 1995-1999 Contract [RESTRICTED], 9.1.9; 1.0
      - Clinical Practice Negotiations Sessions [RESTRICTED], March 20-21, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 3)
      - E-mail correspondence [RESTRICTED], September 1994-April 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 4)
      - Ground Rules for Negotiations [RESTRICTED], February 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 5)
      - Letter Agreement-Joint Committee on Health Benefits Amendment to List of Prospective Procedure Review procedures [RESTRICTED], May-June 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 6)
      - Letters Sent and Received [RESTRICTED], July 1994-September 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 7)
      - Memoranda to UUP Negotiations Committee and Team [RESTRICTED], June 1994-December 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 8)
      - Memoranda to UUP Negotiations Committee and Team [RESTRICTED], January 1995-August 1995; April 1996; March 1997-June 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 9)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between UUP and State [RESTRICTED], July 16, 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 10)
      - Negotiating Team Meeting Notes [RESTRICTED], September 1994-February 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 11)
      - Negotiations Bulletins, Nos. 1-3 [RESTRICTED], September 1994-April 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 12)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #1 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995-March 10, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 13)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #2 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], March 15, 1995-March 16, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 14)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #3 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], March 26, 1995-December 1, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 15)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #4 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], December 7, 1995-January 10, 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 16)
      - Negotiations Sessions Notebook #5 (in shorthand) [RESTRICTED], January 11, 1996-February 2, 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 17)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Four Special Colleges (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 18)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Fourteen Colleges (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 19)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Institutional Types (by type) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 20)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Medical Schools (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 21)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-Technical Colleges (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 22)
      - Negotiations Surveys Response Frequencies-University Centers (by campus) [RESTRICTED], November 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 23)
      - Proposals and Responses status chart; text of proposals from Voice [RESTRICTED], June 18, 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 24)
      - State Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 25)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 11, 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 26)
      - Team and Committee Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 11-13, 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 27)
      - Team and Committee Meeting (transcript and committee reports) [RESTRICTED], November 11-13, 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 28)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], December 15, 1994 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 29)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], January 8-9, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 30)
      - Team Meetings (miscellaneous handouts) [RESTRICTED], December 1995-January 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 31)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], February 10-13, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 32)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], March 2-3, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 33)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], August 17, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 34)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], October 13, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 35)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 16, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 36)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], November 30, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 37)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], March 26, 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 38)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], September 19, 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 39)
      - Team Meeting (handouts) [RESTRICTED], July 10, 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 40)
      - Team Meetings (miscellaneous handouts) [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.10, Folder 41)
      - Tentative Contract Agreement -- special negotiations bulletin mailed to members [RESTRICTED], August 18, 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 42)
      - Transcripts - Negotiations Sessions and Negotiations Team [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995-March 21, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 43)
      - Transcripts - Negotiations Sessions and Negotiations Team [RESTRICTED], March 23, 1995-December 14, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 44)
      - Transcripts - Negotiations Sessions and Negotiations Team [RESTRICTED], January 1996-April 13, 1996 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 45)
      - UUP Contract Proposal "Actual Language" [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.10, Folder 46)
      - UUP Counterproposal [RESTRICTED], March 28, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 47)
      - UUP Crisis Bulletin (vols. 2-11) and News Release [RESTRICTED], February 1, 1995-April 7, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 48)
      - UUP Negotiations Committee and Team Lists [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.1.10, Folder 49)
      - UUP Proposals [RESTRICTED], February 23, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 50)
      - UUP Proposals - drafts, summaries, talking points [RESTRICTED], February-March 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 51)
      - UUP Supplemental Contract Proposals [RESTRICTED], March 15, 1995 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 52)
      - Voice issues re: tentative contract and contract ratification [RESTRICTED], September-October 1997 (Box VI.1.10, Folder 53)
    - Subseries 1.10 - 1999-2003 Contract [RESTRICTED], 9.1.10; 0.17
      Text of final contract and addendum to contract; negotiations bulletin sent to members with text of, and commentary on, contract; tabulated results of survey of members used in preparation for negotiations.
      - 1998 Negotiations Survey Data [RESTRICTED], November 1998 (Box VI.1.11, Folder 1)
      - Addendum to Agreement between the of New York and UUP [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.1.11, Folder 2)
      - Agreement between State of New York and UUP (booklet) [RESTRICTED], July 2, 1999 (Box VI.1.11, Folder 3)
      - Special Negotiations Bulletin--text of tentative agreement with commentary [RESTRICTED], August 20, 1999 (Box VI.1.11, Folder 4)
  - Series 2: Non-Contract Specific Materials, 1971-1989; 9.2; 1.0
    - Subseries 2.1 - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1972-1989; 9.2.1; 0.25
      Correspondence between UUP and the Governor's Office of Employee Relations, reports on collective bargaining in higher education, memoranda of understanding between UUP and the State on evaluation and promotion of professionals, negotiation surveys and other correspondence and materials not obviously related to a specific contract or that overlap contract years.
      - Collected Materials-"Contract Issues" (including tenure, retrenchment, less than full year appointments, and tuition assistance) [RESTRICTED], 1974-1981 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 1)
      - Contract Ratification Procedures [RESTRICTED], ca. 1979? (Box VI.2.1, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence with GOER [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 3)
      - "Higher Education Collective Bargaining: Other than Faculty Personnel", Volume 1, National Center for the Study of Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, Baruch College, CUNY [RESTRICTED], December 1974 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 4)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State of New York and UUP regarding health insurance coverage [RESTRICTED], November 17, 1982 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 5)
      - Memorandum of Understanding Relating to Evaluation and Promotion Systems for Professional Employees in the State University of New York (booklet) [RESTRICTED], April 1977 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 6)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State University of New York and UUP Relating to Systems of Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees (reprint) [RESTRICTED], November 1983 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 7)
      - Memorandum of Understanding between State University of New York and UUP Relating to Systems of Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Employees (revised) [RESTRICTED], August 8, 1989 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 8)
      - Public Employee Federation negotiations with State [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 9)
      - "Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Agreement between the City University of New York and the Professional Staff Congress/CUNY September 1, 1980-August 31, 1982" [RESTRICTED], May 20, 1981 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 10)
      - "Revision of the Board of Trustees Policies", Article XI-Appointment of [Non-Teaching] Professional Staff [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.2.1, Folder 11)
      - Safety and Health Notes/Model Contract [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.2.1, Folder 12)
      - SPA Questionnaire and Summary of Results [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 13)
      - SUNY Board of Trustees Policies [RESTRICTED], 1975; 1983 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 14)
      - Survey results (?) [RESTRICTED], undated (Box VI.2.1, Folder 15)
    - Subseries 2.2 - Clinical Practice Management Plans [RESTRICTED], 1971-1985; 9.2.2; 0.75
      Correspondence and draft language for clinical practice management plans for medical and dental schools. "Collected Materials" also consist of correspondence, proposals, and draft agreements, and were put in chronological order during processing. There are substantial gaps within the time periods covered by each folder. There are also large gaps (sometimes a year or more) between the dates of some materials and when UUP received them. The date of receipt by UUP was used when determining chronological order. There is a limited amount of materials on clinical practice management plans included with the negotiations materials for individual contracts found in Series 1 in this Subgroup.
      - Agreement between State and SPA re: clinical practice [RESTRICTED], January 3, 1974 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 16)
      - Agreement Drafts [RESTRICTED], 1974-1982 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 17)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], January 1974-July 1977 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 18)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], July 1977-February 1981 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 19)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 20)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], April 1981-August 1982 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 21)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], August 1982-January 1984 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 22)
      - Collected Materials [RESTRICTED], January 1984-June 1985 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 23)
      - Collected Materials-Medical and Dental Faculty/Clinical Practice (?) [RESTRICTED], April-October 1976 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 24)
      - Collected Materials-HSC Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 25)
      - "Faculty Salary Compensation from Research Grants and Contracts at SUNY Downstate Medical Center", Report of Ad Hoc Committee [RESTRICTED], December 3, 1980 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 26)
      - Stony Brook-Dental Plans, Correspondence and Notes [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983; 1983 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 27)
      - Stony Brook Medical/Dental Schools Plan, Correspondence, Notes [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 28)
      - Upstate Medical Center Plans and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 29)
      - Upstate Medical Center/Syracuse Plan and Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box VI.2.1, Folder 30)
  - Series 3: Negotiations Surveys [RESTRICTED], 1988-1994; 9.3; 11.0
    This series contains the compiled results of membership surveys conducted by UUP in 1988, 1990, and 1994, as part of its preparations for upcoming contract negotiations. It also includes those survey forms with additional handwritten comments from the member completing the survey. Although for the most part anonymous, these comments document the concerns of UUP members in their own words. Because the information from uncommented forms was already captured in the compiled results, they were not retained as part of this collection.
    Survey topics have included academic freedom and professional development/campus environment; working conditions and benefits; health science centers (1990 and 1994 surveys); part-time employment (1988 survey); appointment, evaluation and promotion; contract management; facilities and technology (1994 survey); and salary items. Demographic questions about respondents (such as campus and appointment status) are also included. Compiled results for 1988 and 1990 were generated in various formats-by campus, rank, type of campus (i.e, university center, health science center, four-year college, two-year college) and various other permutations (gender, academic, professional, librarian, research, health practitioner, resident, part-time employees, and UUP leadership). For 1994, only totals and a break down by part-time employees, academics, and professionals are available in this series. See Subseries 1.9 and 4.2 in this Subgroup for other compiled results for the 1994 survey. For the most part, the 1994 survey forms are organized by chapter, while forms for 1988 and 1990 are arranged by the control number assigned to the form when it was returned to UUP.
    In addition to the regular negotiations survey, as part of negotiations preparations in 1994, a separate "Member Suggestion Form" (which appears to have been distributed in connection with member meetings held on campuses to get input for the upcoming negotiations issues) was used to obtain anecdotal information to support UUP's negotiations demands. Unlike the survey forms, the vast majority of which are anonymous, the member suggestion forms include the name of the individual making the comment. Subseries 4.2 in this Subgroup has some additional member suggestion forms.
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results Grand Totals [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 05 (Box VI.3.1, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results General Statistics by position, rank, chapter grouping, chapter, and position, October 5 & 6 [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box VI.3.1, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Rank [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 05 (Box VI.3.1, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Chapter [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 05 (Box VI.3.1, Folder 4)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Chapter/Rank [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 05 (Box VI.3.1, Folder 5-6)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Chapter Grouping [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 05 (Box VI.3.2, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results by Chapter Grouping/Rank [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 05 (Box VI.3.2, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Chapter Grouping/Position [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 06 (Box VI.3.2, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Position/Rank [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 06 (Box VI.3.2, Folder 4-5)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Rank/Position [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 06 (Box VI.3.2, Folder 6)
    - 1988 Survey-Compiled Results By Chapter/Position [RESTRICTED], 1987 October 06 (Box VI.3.2, Folder 7)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1-74 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #77-204 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #206-299 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #300-407 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 4)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #409-538 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 5)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #544-649 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 6)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #651-799 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 7)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #800-907 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 8)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #909-1029 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 9)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1033-1153 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 10)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1155-1310 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 11)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1311-1434 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 12)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1436-1529 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 13)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1533-1669 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 14)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1671-1899 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 15)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1900-1954 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 16)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #1955-2073 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 17)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2074-2179 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 18)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2180-2251 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 19)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2252-2305 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.3, Folder 20)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2306-2360 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2361-2418 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2419-2469 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2470-2524 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 4)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2525-2575 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 5)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2576-2630 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 6)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2631-2684 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 7)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2685-2739 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 8)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2740-2792 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 9)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2793-2857 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 10)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2861-2957 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 11)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2960-3067 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 12)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #2070-3163 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 13)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3165-3259 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 14)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3260-3374 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 15)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3377-3479 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 16)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3480-3599 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 17)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3600-3719 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 18)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3722-3829 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.4, Folder 19)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3830-3929 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 1)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #3932-4035 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 2)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4036-4173 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 3)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4176-4298 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 4)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4300-4424 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 5)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4426-4559 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 6)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4562-4667 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 7)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4672-4789 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 8)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4790-4898 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 9)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #4900-5014 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 10)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #5015-5124 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 11)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #5127-5247 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 12)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #5250-5374 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 13)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #5376-5475 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 14)
    - 1988 Survey, Forms #5442-5474 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 15)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #02-131 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 16)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #134-241 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 17)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #246-352 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 18)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #356-466 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.5, Folder 19)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #467-548 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 1)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #550-682 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 2)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #684-789 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 3)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #790-883 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 4)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #884-984 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 5)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #985-1097 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 6)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1101-1299 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 7)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1300-1429 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 8)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1430-1484 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 9)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1485-1549 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 10)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1550-1745 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 11)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1746-1919 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 12)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #1920-2039 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 13)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #2040-2225 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 14)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #2226-2340 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 15)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #2341-2398 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 16)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #2431-2559 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 17)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #2560-2659 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 18)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #2660-2794 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.6, Folder 19)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3426-3489 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 1)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3490-3549 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 2)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3550-3599 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 3)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3600-3655 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 4)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3656-3709 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 5)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3710-3764 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 6)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3765-3819 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 7)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3820-3874 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 8)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3875-3934 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 9)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #3935-4259 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 10)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4260-4315 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 11)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4316-4369 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 12)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4370-4419 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 13)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4420-4529 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 14)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4530-4619 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 15)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4620-4735 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 16)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4736-4829 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 17)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4830-4959 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 18)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #4960-5084 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.7, Folder 19)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #5085-5149 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.8, Folder 0A)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #5150-5299 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.8, Folder 0B)
    - 1990 Survey, Forms #5300-5349 [RESTRICTED] (Box VI.3.8, Folder 0C)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, All Campuses [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 1)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, No Response re: Campus [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 2)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Special Institutions [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 3)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Two-Year Institutions [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 4)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Four-Year Institutions [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 5)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Health Science Centers [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 6)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Universities [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 7)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Albany [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 8)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Binghamton [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 9)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, SUNY-Buffalo [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 10)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, SUNY-Stony Brook [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 11)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Buffalo HSC [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 12)
    - 1990 Survey-Compiled Results, Stony Brook HSC [RESTRICTED], 1990 October 17 (Box VI.3.8, Folder 13)